Japanese-Style Music Collection  20+ Tracks

This is free trial version. Only 2 Tracks are included.

http://u3d.as/1DKq
Get Link and See FULL VERSION


Best Japanese-Style Music Collection 

Powerful and emotional music which are used Japanese traditional instruments, Shakuhachi, Koto, and Shamisen. This perfectly fits for battles, emotional scenes and trailer films. There are many genres of music.
In this package you'll find 1 vocal track and 20 instrumental tracks.
All of the wav tracks are available as high quality 16 bit, and high quality re-mastered for using in games.
And, this pack includes ogg seamless loop with all music tracks.



-------Version Released

Oct 9th 2019 First release



------

Content


09. Kiyoku Yawaragi
18. Shiokaze


Produced by ISAo.
http://airyluvs.com
isao@airyluvs.com

*If you want to order new music or arrangement, please contact to me :)

Thanks.
2019/10/9
